If they have managed the winter well, it is very outlook it is what I am looking for.
That they are out flying, I see that.
I see that outputs on some cups.
But the bees seem to be spiked.
And the winds are knocked out here on the slopes.
We'll take a look here.
There is plenty of bees all over the surface.
So that...
Heat has these.
Then we lift off.
Then we look here.
It looks nice.
Good with bees.
Maybe these frames would be removed.
They are empty.
Probably there has been no fry in them.
Then I will remove these frames.
In a week.
Or maybe we would do it today.
But then we are already in the spring development.
There are no fry here.
So probably the fry is at the top.
And then we lift this box.
No, here is fry.
So then you can't remove such frames.
But then we have to change the frames.
Dives, but we do not today.
Look here, that's a lot of fry.
Okay.
Then we can re -put this.
Say that this has been in a good winter.
We can take the opportunity to replace it.
Or turn on to the one we usually do.
We can put this away.
Not much food left.
Not here either.
And there we have the bee queen.
Then we know.
We have seen fry in the lower box.
We'll see if we find anything more.
No covered fry here.
This indicates that there is quite a bit of food left.
Yes.
This must be food.
No, this must have food.
There is no food here.
On both sides.
So that they can handle a few weeks at least.
Then that frame is also quite full.
Oh.
So there are two frames just full.
And so is a frame that is half full.
So there is a 5 kilo honey left.
But we will give them more as soon as the weather gets a little better.
Then we will increase it.
And then we will see what the bottom looks like on this bee community.
So then you see that.
To.
The bottoms work with this aeration.
Look here huh.
So.
But you see they have shit.
Here anyway.
Has it been a bit outdated at the entrance.
But they have not done anything on the frames.
And then it is nice to be able to just turn on.
This bottom.
Block out the exit backwards and have in one.
Exit on the front.
Here it was fry.
And it was a shame it.
Because I had thought I would have removed.
This box.
So we do so.
We remove it anyway.
And choose.
This one as a breeding room.
Or rather.
The one as a breeding room.
At the bottom.
Oh.
There was food.
Almost no food.
I was expecting me to find fry here in this box.
Since.
It is.
So much bees here.
But I see nothing.
I've only seen the fry in it.
That bottom box.
But it is good with food here.
But that's clean.
It is not.
It is not downhill.
Out of.
Here we see.
That it is good with bees.
And it's hot here.
So we lift off and turn on the bottom.
So we'll see what it looks like inside the boxes.
Here it seems to be old frames that we should try to change.
When we turn on the bottom we see what it looks like.
Here we see a lot of dead bees.
And they.
We shovel down.
The impaired.
It's a little pronounced.
But we'll see what it looks like on the bottom.
So.
It is more humid on this than on the others.
What it may be due to.
But for the time being we turn on the bottom.
After all, there are frames that should be removed.
We will see what the others look like.
We don't find any fry here.
So we shake them off.
And then.
Yes.
And this is not a fry.
Without it is old food.
We can remove that too.
That is also old food.
It may be that it is.
Yes it is crystallized honey that they had difficulty removed.
There is some crystallized honey.
It may remain at the bottom here.
Then I remove the latter.
Damn.
It is one up there and crawls [a bee].
So there were a 34 frames with crystallized honey here.
And it may remain until further notice.
So maybe it can't eat so we can change it for a little better honey.
And here, this one was heavy so it could go away all that.
Because here is food.
You feel that on the weight.
Pretty little food on this page.
Then it is well on the opposite side.
And here it starts to come.
Slightly.
And here we have bee queen.
It looks good with fry then.
Then we can leave these in peace.
Because here there is food.
Then we will change only the lower box.
Because they have done well with the honey too.
And that's what I was worried about.
If there is any crap on the frames.
After all, it is not.
Rather, it is crystallized honey here.
Which they have had a hard time ...
... to get out.
You see clean frames here.
Fine.
We'll see a bump on this one.
Here are old frames that we have set ...
... in a group down to just be able to change easily.
In the spring.
But even those ...
... is pretty clean.
So they have not suffered any outspoken or ...
... and use the other side.
And it looks clean ...
... on the frames I think.
No shit.
We can only see if we find ...
... fry here.
It's honey.
They are doing well.
It doesn't look like any fry.
Here is the fry.
Do you see it
Here.
And there goes the bee queen, I see.
Then it's just that ...
... put it again and remove that one ...
...one...
... the box ...
... as the old frames were in.
Oh here.
This was ...
... this was food.
Here are frames that have ended up at the bottom of a box ...
... where there was a fry in the frames.
And I will remove them here.
They are dark and fry -free.
And they can go directly to the sunwax melt ...
... who is starting to serve yesterday.
Should you draw any conclusions on the interior with honey ...
There were no disarray with ...
... that it would be our drone mothers.
So I'm happy with this.
We look forward to ...
... spring and flowering here.
The trees are already full of buds.
Cherry trees, it teases out of bud ...
... in the branches.
And also apple trees.
So it looks good in Bigården.
Happy Easter on you, we will hear.
[Closing bisurr]